이전에 "100"에 ...
Previously on "The 100"...
우리 모두 사람을 저장하는 유일한 방법
The only way to save both our people
우리가 함께 가입하는 경우입니다.
is if we join together.
내부에 사람이 없다면, 자신의 방어를 낮출
Without someone on the inside
to lower their defenses,
군대의 쓸모.
an army's useless.
당신은 가야한다.
You should go.
나는 터널을 통해 당신을 얻을 수 있습니다.
I can get you through the tunnels.
어떻게 아래로 나를보기에 대한, 마야?
How about getting me down, Maya?
움직이지 마!
Don't move!
아아!
Agh!
양육권에 데려가.
Take him into custody.
미안 해요. 그들은 지금 내에서 자신의 주문을.
I'm sorry. They take
their orders from me now.
검역소에 아버지를 넣습니다.
Put my father in quarantine.
네, 대통령.
Yes, Mr. President.
그들은 이미 자신의 혈액을 사용하는
They're already using their blood,
사물이 거 정말 빨리 여기에 추한 있습니다.
and things are gonna get
ugly in here real fast.
하지 마십시오!
No!
나는 당신의 지도자에 대한 메시지가 있습니다.
I have a message for your leader.
우리는 그를 위해오고있어.
We're coming for him.
우리 사람들이 가자, 우리는 당신이 살고 드리겠습니다.
Let our people go, and we'll let you live.
그것은 다시 마운트 날씨에 8 시간 거리입니다.
It's an 8-hour walk back to Mount Weather.
당신은거야 그것은 6으로이 일을 할 수 있습니다.
You're gonna do it in 6.
헉!
Ugh!
선생님, 당신은 너무 멀리있어 ...
Sir, you're too far...
문에서, 너무 멀리.
From the door, way too far.
심호흡. 나에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오.
Just breathe. Don't worry about me.
당신은 당신이, 선생님을하지 않았나요? 응?
You did it, didn't you, sir? Huh?
골수 처리, 그것은했다.
The marrow treatment, it worked.
우리는 중위, 그것을했다.
We did it, Lieutenant.
땅은 우리입니다.
The ground is ours.
- 동기화 및 chamallow에 의해 수정 - - www.addic7ed.com -
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
우리는 시간 동안 갇혀 있었어요.
We've been locked up for hours.
경우는 벨라미는 ...
If it was Bellamy...
그것은 벨라미했다.
It was Bellamy.
나는 그가 여기 말하고있다.
I'm telling you he's here.
좋아.
All right.
그것은 이해가되지 않습니다.
It doesn't make any sense.
내가 본 것을 알고있다.
I know what I saw.
다시는.
Not again.
모두를 백업합니다. 백업합니다.
Back up, everyone. Back up.
이동!
Move!
- 아니, 아니! - 이봐, 이봐! 그녀는 꺼져!
- No, no!
- Hey, hey! Get off her!
아니, 그녀.
No, not her.
그녀는 회복하는 데 더 많은 시간을 필요로한다.
She needs more time to recover.
이거요.
This one.
아니! 잠깐!
No! Wait, wait!
안돼, 제발! 아니!
No, please! No!
그만!
Stop!
당신은 우리에게이 일을 계속 할 수 없습니다.
You can't keep doing this to us.
대통령 월러스는 우리가 갈 수 있다고 말했다.
President Wallace said we could go.
즉, 대통령 월러스는 명령에 더 이상 없습니다.
That President Wallace
is no longer in command.
그는 건강상의 이유로 사임했다.
He had to step down for health reasons.
나는 이렇게 돼서 미안 해요.
I'm sorry it has to be like this.
난 당신이 우리 모두에게 매우 특별한 걸 알고 있기를 바랍니다.
I hope you know you're all
incredibly special to us.
밖으로 취소합니다. 이동합니다.
Clear out. Go.
그는 아직 체크하고 있는가?
Has he checked in yet?
하지 마십시오.
No.
당신은 다른 사람의거야 시도하고 방주 안에 당신을 촬영을 걱정?
You worried someone's gonna try and
take a shot at you inside the Ark?
외부 라이더 기다립니다.
Wait outside, Ryder.
LEXA의 명령.
Lexa's orders.
무엇이든간에, 클라크.
Whatever, Clarke.
그는 늦었어요.
He's late.
뭔가 그에게 무슨 일이 있었 어떻게하나요?
What if something's happened to him?
그는 괜찮을거야.
He'll be fine.
당신은 바빴어요.
You've been busy.
왜 댐에 초점을 맞추고있다?
Why are you focusing on the dam?
나는 산 안개는 우리의 우선 순위를이었다 당신을 말했다.
I told you acid fog was our priority.
벨라미가 분산 시스템에 눈을 얻을 때까지,
Until Bellamy gets eyes
on their dispersal system,
단지 너무 많은 내가 할 수있다.
there's only so much I can do.
파인. 댐에 대해 말해.
Fine. Tell me about the dam.
우리는 자신의 전원을 차단 할 수 있습니까?
Can we cut off their power?
아마. 나는 아직도 몇 가지와 함께 연주하고 있습니다.
Maybe. I'm still playing with a few things.
당신은 어떻게이 많은 만들었습니다?
How many of these have you made?
단 두 지금까지,하지만 ...
Only two so far, but...
두? 그게 충분하지 않습니다.
Two? That's not enough.
모든 곳에서 수확이있을 것입니다.
There will be Reapers everywhere.
고주파 톤 제너레이터는 나무에 클라크 성장하지 않습니다.
High-frequency tone generators
don't grow on trees, Clarke.
윅은 부품 scrounging된다.
Wick is scrounging for parts.
, 레이븐, Tondc 떠날에 대한 생각
Raven, I am about to leave for Tondc,
여기서 LEXA 모든 12 땅볼 씨족의 머리
where Lexa and the heads
of all 12 Grounder clans
내가 우리가 갈 거라고 얘기를 기다리고있다,
are waiting for me to tell them we're a go,
그들은 여전히?? 산 안개가 있기 때문에 단지 우리가 갈 아니에요
only we're not a go because
they still have acid fog,
우리는 두 톤 제너레이터가있다.
and we only have two tone generators.
이봐. 우리는 준비가되어있을거야. 우리는 것이다.
Hey. We'll be ready. We will.
방주 역, 들립니까?
Ark Station, do you read me?
거기 누구?
Anybody there?
벨라미, 당신은 늦었 어.
Bellamy, you're late.
매 3 시간마다 3 시간을 의미합니다.
Every 3 hours means every 3 hours.
당신은을 통해 있습니까?
Are you through?
당신이 산 안개의 원인을 찾을 수 있나요?
Have you found the source of the acid fog?
아뇨 거 기다릴 필요가 있어요.
No. That's gonna have to wait.
무엇? 번호 아무것도 그것보다 더 중요한 것은 없습니다.
What? No. Nothing is
more important than that.
우리의 친구입니다.
Our friends are.
그들은 기숙사에서 데리고 시작하고
They're starting to take them from the dorm
한번에 한 몇 시간마다.
one at a time every few hours.
어디에서 촬영?
Taking them where?
모르겠어요.
I don't know.
우리는 그들을 따라하려고
We tried to follow them,
그러나 그들은 분류 수준에 갔다.
but they went to a classified level.
마야 통기 시스템의 회로도를 빌려
Maya borrowed the
schematics of the vent system
그녀의 상사에서, 나는 여전히 수있는 방법을 찾기 위해 노력하고있어.
from her boss, and I'm still
trying to find a way in.
뭐?
Anything?
내가 길을 찾은 것 같아,
I think I found a path,
하지만 이건 빡빡합니다.
but it's gonna be tight.
여기에 까마귀가 요구 무전기입니다
Here's the walkie Raven asked for
와 이어 버드.
and the earbud.
우리는 그를 모바일 만들려고하고 그래서 그는 어디에서 우리에게 이야기 할 수 있습니다.
We're going to make him mobile so
he can talk to us from anywhere.
벨라미는, 당신이 그들을 찾을 수있다.
Bellamy, you have to find them.
그게 계획이다.
That's the plan.
그렇지 않으면,이 모든 것이 아무것도입니다.
If you don't, all of this is for nothing.
그래.
Yeah.
곧 돌아 올게요.
I'll be right back.
난 당신이 Tondc에가는 줄 알았는데.
I thought you were going to Tondc.
계획이 변경되었습니다.
Plans have changed.
난 여기있을거야.
I'm staying here.
지휘관은 당신을 기다리고 있어요.
The commander's expecting you.
마운트 날씨 안에 우리의 사람들은 문제가 있습니다.
Our people inside Mount
Weather are in trouble.
나는 그들이 확인 걸 알고 전까지는 아무데도 안가요.
I'm not going anywhere
until I know they're ok.
그리고 당신은 여기에서 그들을 위해 무엇을 할 수 있습니까?
And what can you do for them from here?
당신은 내 자리에 Tondc로 이동합니다.
You'll go to Tondc in my place.
LEXA 당신을 존중합니다.
Lexa respects you.
내가 할 수있는 나는 곧 도착합니다.
I'll get there soon as I can.
클라크는 기다립니다.
Clarke, wait.
그것을 치워.
Put it away.
클라크는 훌륭한 지도자 수단 인
Clarke, being a good leader means
아는 어떤 싸움 전투.
knowing which battles to fight.
그리고 어떤을 위임합니다. 나는 알고있다.
And which to delegate. I know.
난 당신이 Tondc에 갈 필요가하십시오.
Please I need you to go to Tondc.
파인.
Fine.
나는 갈거야.
I'll go.
감사합니다.
Thank you.
그것은 무엇인가?
What is it?
케인은 설명합니다.
Kane will explain.
아마도 어머니가 이동해야합니다.
Perhaps your mother should go.
그녀는 여전히 후 장관이다.
She is still the chancellor after all.
어떤 그녀는 여기에 필요한 왜이다.
Which is why she's needed here.
무거운 왕관을있다.
Heavy lies the crown.
그녀는 왕관을 착용해서는 안
She shouldn't be wearing the crown,
당신은 그녀를 백업 할 수 없습니다.
and you shouldn't be backing her up.
그 무엇입니까?
What is that?
참고. 셀 로니 어스 사라 졌어요.
A note. Thelonious is gone.
그는 이틀 기다려야 싱클레어에게
He told Sinclair to wait two days
우리에게 그것을 제공하기 전에.
before giving that to us.
빛의 도시입니다.
The City of Light.
그는 다시 우리를 구하기 위해 돌아오고 말한다.
He says he's coming back to save us again.
그는 12 명 12 건을했다.
He took 12 people, 12 guns.
당신은 그를 갈 수 없습니다. 우리는 사람들을 절약 할 수 없습니다.
You can't go after him.
We can't spare the men.
오, 그것에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오. 클라크는하지 않았어
Oh, don't worry about
it. Clarke wouldn't let me
심지어 내가 원한다면.
even if I wanted to.
행운을 빌어 요, 셀 로니 어스.
Godspeed, Thelonious.
선생님, 당신은 아무것도를 인식합니까?
Sir, do you recognize anything?
자신의 텐트는 여기 근처에 있었다.
Their tent was near here.
나는 그것을 확신합니다.
I'm sure of it.
무슨 일이야? 너희들이 될 곳 더있어?
What's the matter? You guys
got someplace better to be?
당신은 사람을 볼?
You see anyone?
_
우리는 당신에게 어떤 해를 의미하지 않습니다.
We mean you no harm.
당신은 영어를하십니까?
Do you speak English?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
What do you want?
아무것도. 당신이 손을 사용할 수있는 것 같습니다.
Nothing. It looks like
you could use a hand.
여기서 혼자 뭐하는거야?
What are you doing out here alone?
내 동생과 나는, 빛의 도시로가는 길에 있었다
My brother and I were on
our way to the City of Light,
및 wastelanders 공격.
and wastelanders attacked.
그들은 모든 것을 우리의 모든 물을 우리의 말을했다.
They took our horse, all
our water, everything.
그들은 그를 죽였다.
They killed him.
이 카트 내가 가진 모든 것입니다.
This cart is all I have left.
그녀에게 물을 준다.
Give her some water.
우와, 아니, 아니, 아니, 아니, 아니.
Whoa, no, no, no, no, no.
우리는 거의 여기에 자신에 대한 충분한 있습니다.
We barely have enough for ourselves here.
나를 다시 터치, 나는 당신을 겁니다.
Touch me again, and I'll end you.
noncriminal 방법으로.
In a noncriminal way.
괜찮아요.
It's ok.
우리는뿐만 아니라, 빛의 도시에가는 길에있어.
We're on our way to the
City of Light, as well.
당신의 이름은 무엇입니까?
What's your name?
Emor.
Emori.
사각 지대에있는 모든 사람
Everyone in the dead zone
빛의 도시를 찾고 있습니다.
is looking for the City of Light.
거의 아무도 그것을 발견한다.
Almost no one finds it.
난 당신이 얻을 수 있습니다.
I can get you there.
당신은 내 카트를 끌어합니다.
If you pull my cart.
완료.
Done.
카스피, 첫 번째 변화에있어.
Caspian, you're on the first shift.
물 주셔서 감사합니다.
Thanks for the water.
그것은 어 ... 그것은 아무 문제가 없었다입니다.
It's, uh... it was no problem.
확인을 클릭합니다. 당신이 지금에있어 어디 그래서 알려주십시오.
Ok. So tell us where you're at now.
내가 교차로에 있어요. 어떤 방법으로?
I'm at an intersection. Which way?
확인을 클릭합니다. 그는 단지 공기 여과 시스템을 통과
Ok. He just passed the
air filtration system
여기에 대해 그를두고이 바닥에.
on this floor, which puts him about here.
벨라미는, 우리는 당신이 가까운 것 같아요.
Bellamy, we think you're close.
연구소는 앞으로 최대해야한다.
The lab should be up ahead.
가능성은 당신이 더 구체적인 될 수 있는가?
Any chance you can be more specific?
신경 쓰지 마. 나는이 있어요.
Never mind. I got this.
그게 드릴 수 있습니까?
Is that a drill?
골수 추출.
Bone marrow extraction.
당신의 마지막 치료를위한 준비
You ready for the last treatment
당신은, 중위가 필요합니다?
you'll ever need, Lieutenant?
당신은 아무 생각이 없습니다.
You have no idea.
나는 신선한 공기를 호흡??하기 위해 내 인생을 기다렸다.
I've waited my whole
life to breathe fresh air.
즉, 에머슨입니다.
That's Emerson.
이 비밀 군대 다시 연락하자
Let's get back to this secret army
것을 그녀는이 주장하고있다.
that she claims to have.
그녀는 수도 아무 말도
She tell you anything that might
우리는 그것을 찾는 데 도움이?
help us find it?
드릴링을 중지하십시오.
Stop drilling, please.
죽음 후에 추출을위한 창
The window for extraction after death
믿을 수 없을만큼 짧다.
is incredibly short.
난 단지 분 필요합니다.
I only need a minute.
아니, 선생님. 군대에 대한 아무것도 없습니다.
No, sir. Nothing about the army.
그녀는 그녀가 당신을 위해 오는 말 했는가
She did say she was coming for you
우리가 할 수있는 경우와 그녀의 사람들이 갈 것을
and that if we let her people go
그녀는 우리의 사람들의 생활 드리겠습니다.
she'll let our people live.
그러기 엔 조금 늦었어요.
It's a little late for that.
나는, 선생님 실패 죄송합니다.
I'm sorry I failed, sir.
아니, 괜찮아요. 우리는 일 오늘 밤을 마무리합니다.
No, it's ok. We'll finish the job tonight.
휘트먼은 그냥 라디오로 방송.
Whitman just radioed in.
분명히 전쟁 협의회가있다
Apparently there's a war council meeting
자신의 마을 중 하나에 오늘 밤 일어나고,
happening tonight in one of their villages,
모든 지도자가 될거.
and all the leaders are gonna be there.
선생님, 기분이 좋다. 내가 팀을 보자
Sir, I feel good. Let me take a team out
그리고 휘트먼을 지원합니다.
and support Whitman.
호 그는 혼자 경우 발견되는 작은 기회가있다.
No. He has less chance of
being spotted if he's alone.
선생님, 휘트먼의 좋은,
Sir, Whitman's good,
그러나 그는 혼자 그 많은 목표를 꺼낼 수 없습니다.
but he can't take out
that many targets alone.
어떤 우린 미사일을 사용하는 이유입니다.
Which is why we're gonna use a missile.
이 시간, 우리는 그리울 아니에요.
This time, we're not gonna miss.
당신이 모든 것을 듣고 알려주세요.
Please tell me you heard all that.
우리는 그것을 들었다.
We heard it.
우리는 그들에게 경고해야합니다.
We have to warn them.
케인은 무선을 했습니까?
Did Kane take a radio?
아니 이것은 유일한 걸림 해제 주파수이다.
No. This is the only unjammed frequency.
우리는 벨라미 오픈을 유지해야합니다.
We have to keep it open for Bellamy.
지금 떠날 경우에, 나는 시간이 그것을 만들 수 있습니다.
If I leave now, I can
make it there in time.
시간이 폭파 될, 당신은 의미한다.
In time to be blown up, you mean.
내가 돌아올 때, 나는 알고 싶어
When I get back, I want to know
우리의 친구는 안전하고 산 안개가 다운되었습니다.
our friends are safe
and the acid fog is down.
당신은 그렇게 처리 할 수?? 있습니까?
Can you handle that?
그래, 우리는 그것을 처리 할 수?? 있습니다. 이동합니다.
Yeah, we can handle it. Go.
클라크는 기다립니다.
Clarke, wait.
내가 떠날 때 옥타 비아는 Tondc에 있었다.
Octavia was in Tondc when I left.
인가 ... 음, 그녀는 ...
Is... is she, um...
그녀는 여기에 있습니다. 그녀는 안전합니다.
She's here. She's safe.
확인을 클릭합니다. 좋은. 도 안전합니다.
Ok. Good. Be safe, too.
나는 것이다.
I will.
회의 Tondc에 옥타 비아 년대.
Octavia's in Tondc for the meeting.
당신이 왜 거짓말?
Why'd you lie?
벨라미는 산만 할 수 없습니다.
Bellamy can't be distracted.
그것은 아무 도움이되지 않습니다.
It helps no one.
이봐.
Hey.
수행 폭파되지.
Don't get blown up.
_
마지막으로, 그들은 여기에 발을 밟은
Last time, they stepped foot here,
우리는 서로 전쟁에 있었다.
we were at war with each other.
이제 12 가문이 함께 싸운다.
Now the 12 clans fight together.
이 날을 기억하십시오. 당신은 같은 일을 다시 보지 못할 수 있습니다.
Remember this day. You may
never see one like it again.
당신은 내가 말한 단어를 듣지 못했어요.
You haven't heard a word I've said.
미안 해요.
Sorry.
벨라미는 이틀 전에 터널에서 링컨 왼쪽
Bellamy left Lincoln in
the tunnels two days ago,
- 그는 ... 다시 없어야합니다 - 링컨은 더 이상 당신의 관심사입니다.
- and he should be back...
- Lincoln is no longer your concern.
봐. 난 당신이 요구했던 걸 모두 했어
Look. I've done everything
you've asked me to do,
나는 계속 그렇게 할 것이다,
and I'll continue to do so,
하지만 이제 당신이 뭘 요구하는지하는 것은 불가능하다.
but what you're asking now is impossible.
내가 요구하는 것도 아니 구요.
I'm not asking.
우리는 전쟁에있어, 그리고 전사는 슬퍼하지 않습니다
We're at war, and a warrior does not mourn
그 그녀는 전투 승리 후까지 잃었다.
those she's lost till
after the battle is won.
다른 초 스탠드 시계를 이동합니다.
Go stand watch with the other seconds.
산에서 자객을 다시 시도합니다.
Assassins from the mountain will try again.
우리는 준비 할 필요가있다.
We need to be ready.
그래서 물어 얻었다.
So I got to ask.
어떻게 당신의 가정을 도랑 만든
What made you ditch your home
지옥에서 해변을 건너 당신의 인생을 위험?
and risk your life to
cross the beach from hell?
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
It doesn't matter.
안돼, 가자. 내 마음을 받아
No. Come on. Take my mind
모든 재미 떨어져 우리는 데있어.
off all the fun we're having.
그것은 떠나 내 결정이 아니었다.
It wasn't my decision to leave.
쫓겨?
Kicked out?
확인을 클릭합니다. 지금은 관심이 있어요. 당신은 뭐라고합니까?
Ok. Now I'm interested. What'd you do?
내가 당신에게하는 경우,
If I told you,
당신은 같은 날 봐하지 않을 것이다.
you would not look at me the same.
아마.
Maybe.
그럼 다시, 나는 당신을 놀라게 수 있습니다.
Then again, I might surprise you.
당신은 어때요?
What about you?
어떻게 데드 존에서 생을 마감 했습니까?
How did you end up in the dead zone?
나는 당신에게 피투성이 세부 사항을 말할 수
I could tell you the gory details,
하지만 당신은이 행성에있는 몇 안되는 사람 중 한 명 이니
but since you're one of the
few people on this planet
누가, 그 순간에 나를 미워하지 않는다
who doesn't hate me at the moment,
나는 그것을 날려하려는 생각하지 않습니다.
I don't think I want to blow it.
지금은 관심이 있어요.
Now I'm interested.
확인을 클릭합니다. 당신은 정말 알고 싶어?
Ok. You really want to know?
나는 두 사람을 살해
I killed two people,
두 개를 죽이려.
tried to kill two more.
내 이유를했지만, 아무도 신경 쓰지.
I had my reasons, but nobody cared.
나는 나쁜 놈이야.
I'm the bad guy.
나는 그것을 날려 버릴 거라고 말했다.
Told you I'd blow it.
내 사람들은 얼룩으로 나를 보았다
My people saw me as a stain
혈통에,
on the bloodline,
뭔가 삭제합니다.
something to erase.
다음을 조입니다.
Then screw them.
나는 그것을 은폐하지 않을 것이다.
I wouldn't cover it up.
나는 그것이 매우 불량한 생각합니다.
I think it's pretty badass.
야생 이여.
Liar.
돌아가! 나는 돌아 가야했다.
Get back! I said get back.
여기에서 우리는 간다. 어서. 마찬가지로 우리는 이야기!
Here we go. Come on. Like we talked about!
링크 업!
Link up!
이거요.
This one.
좋아. 가자.
All right. Let's go.
지금 모두!
Everybody now!
비켜!
Clear the way!
아!
Aah!
이봐!
Hey!
이거 놔!
Let go of me!
당신은 자신을 살해하려고합니까?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
벨라미?
Bellamy?
그냥 닥치고 들어.
Just shut up and listen.
그들은 그들을 죽이고있어.
They're killing them.
그들이 와서 다음 번에, 당신은 다시 싸울 필요
Next time they come, you have to fight back
이것보다 더 열심히, 당신은 이해합니까?
harder than this, do you understand?
여기에. 이 걸릴.
Here. Take this.
모두가 준비.
Get everyone ready.
무엇을위한 준비가 되셨습니까? 계획은 무엇입니까?
Ready for what? What's the plan?
내가 일하고 있어요.
I'm working on it.
단테를 찾을 수 있습니다. 그는 우리 편이다. 그분은 우리를 도와 드리겠습니다.
Find Dante. He's on
our side. He'll help us.
확인을 클릭합니다.
Ok.
이봐! 저기 확인 모든?
Hey! Everything ok over there?
예, 알겠습니다.
Yes, sir.
아악!
Unh!
도와주세요!
Help!
제발, 누가 좀. 아니!
Please, somebody. No!
당신의 저녁 식사, 대통령 월러스.
Your evening meal, President Wallace.
당신은 누구 요?
Who are you?
재스퍼 날을 보냈습니다.
Jasper sent me.
우리는 당신의 도움이 필요합니다.
We need your help.
당신의 아들은 내 친구를 죽이고있다.
Your son is killing my friends.
나는 그들과 동일한 죄수 해요.
I'm a prisoner, same as them.
이 산의 구석 구석을 알고 포로,
A prisoner who knows every
inch of this mountain,
모든 보안 조치.
every security measure.
누가 당신을 돕고?
Who's helping you?
그것은 지금 중요하지 않습니다.
That's not important right now.
클라크는 탈출 후,
After Clarke escaped,
나는이 모든 출구는 강화했다
I had all exits fortified
여분의 감시했습니다.
and put under extra surveillance.
내 아들은 의심의 여지가 변경되었습니다
My son has no doubt changed
이제 모든 액세스 및 입구 코드.
all access and entrance codes by now.
친구도 레벨 5의 떨어져 그것을 확인하지 않습니다.
Your friends will never
even make it off of level 5.
나는 그들이 여기에 죽게하지 않습니다.
I won't let them die here.
미안 해요. 나는 그들이 탈출 할 수 없습니다.
I'm sorry. I can't help them escape.
그러나 나는 그들에게 약간의 시간을 살 수 있습니다.
But I may be able to buy them some time.
Hyah! Hyah!
클라크는, 당신은 그것을했다.
Clarke, you made it.
난 당신이 LEXA 날을해야합니다.
I need you to take me to Lexa.
무슨 일이야?
What's wrong?
아무것도.
Nothing.
벨라미는 준비가되어?
Is Bellamy ready?
그는 산 안개 아래됩니까?
Did he get the acid fog down?
그는 작업입니다.
He's working on it.
휘트먼은 날씨 명령을 마운트합니다.
Whitman to Mount Weather command.
최종 목표는 착륙했다.
Final target has landed.
모든 목표를 차지했다.
All targets accounted for.
알았다. 대통령에 의해 서.
Copy that. Standing by for the president.
하늘 사람들의 클라크가
Clarke of the Sky people has
그녀의 존재로 우리를 영광.
honored us with her presence.
나는 늦게 사령관 죄송 해요.
I'm sorry I'm late, Commander.
당신은 좋은 시간을했다.
You made good time.
나는 산 날씨에 아이들이 괜찮아요 가정합니다.
I assume the kids at Mount Weather are ok.
지금은.
For now.
우리는 개인적으로 이야기 할 수 있습니까?
Can we talk in private?
예. 이 방법.
Yes. This way.
미사일? 당신은 확실 해요?
A missile? You're sure?
예. 우리는 지금 철수 시작해야합니다.
Yes. We have to start evacuating now.
하지 마십시오.
No.
당신은, 아니 LEXA을 무엇을 의미합니까?
What do you mean no, Lexa?
우리가 철수하면, 그들은 우리가 알 수 있습니다
If we evacuate, they'll know we have
자신의 벽 내부의 스파이.
a spy inside their walls.
꼭 그렇지는 않습니다.
Not necessarily.
우리는 위험을 감수 할 수 없습니다.
We can't risk it.
내부에 사람이있는의 점은 무엇인가
What's the point of having an inside man
우리는 그가 우리에게 어떤 행동 할 수없는 경우?
if we can't act on what he tells us?
산 안개가 비활성화되어 있습니까?
Is the acid fog disabled?
우리의 수면 군은 uncaged인가?
Is our sleeping army uncaged?
그리고 벨라미의 작업이 수행되지 않습니다.
Then Bellamy's job is not done.
그가 없으면, 우리는이 전쟁을 이길 수 없습니다.
Without him, we can't win this war.
그래서 당신은 말을하는거야?
So what are you saying?
우리는 아무것도하지 않고,
We just do nothing,
그들이 우리를 폭격하자?
let them bomb us?
그것은 타격이 될 것입니다,
It will be a blow,
그러나 우리 군은 숲 내부 안전합니다,
but our army will be safe inside the woods,
그것은 그들에게 영감을 것입니다.
and it will inspire them.
그리고 우리에 대해 뭐라고?
And what about us?
우리는 지금 빠져.
We slip away right now.
이에 넣습니다.
Put this on.
LEXA, 기다려. 당신은 이해하지 않습니다.
Lexa, wait. You don't understand.
나는 산 날씨를 불러 일으켰다.
I provoked Mount Weather.
나는 벨라미에서 그들을 방해하는 메시지를 보냈습니다.
I sent a message to
distract them from Bellamy.
클라크는, 때때로, 당신은 전쟁을 이길 수있는 전투를 양보해야합니다.
Clarke, sometimes, you have to
concede a battle to win a war.
아니 우리는 씨족의 지도자를 알릴 수있다,
No. We can inform the leaders of the clans,
숲에서 랑데부 지점을 선택합니다.
pick a rendezvous point in the woods.
그들 각각은 개별적으로 미끄러 수 있습니다.
Each of them can slip out separately.
그리고 그들은 얼마나 더 많은 사람들에게 것인가?
And how many more people will they tell?
우리는 어디에서 선을 그어야합니까?
Where do we draw the line?
그럼 모임을 취소,
Well, then cancel the meeting,
뭔가를 불을!
start a fire, something!
클라크는, 우리는이 시간이 없습니다.
Clarke, we don't have time for this.
아니, 아니!
No, no!
이것은 잘못입니다!
This is wrong!
그것은 또한 우리의 유일한 선택, 그리고 당신은 그것을 알고있다.
It's also our only choice, and you know it.
당신은 거기 모두를 해줬어야 했어
You could have warned everyone up there,
하지만 당신은하지 않았다.
but you didn't.
당신은 심지어 자신의 사람들에게 아무것도, 말했다.
You said nothing, not
even to your own people.
이것은, 클라크 전쟁이다. 사람들은 죽는다.
This is war, Clarke. People die.
오늘 진정한 힘을 보여 주었다.
You showed true strength today.
감정이 지금 당신을 멈추게하지 말라.
Don't let emotions stop you now.
이제 갈 시간이다.
It's time to go.
_
장관, 조심해!
Chancellor, look out!
_
쏘지 마!
Hold your fire!
잠깐! 워, 워.
Wait! Whoa, whoa.
모두가 무기를 넣어
Everybody put your weapons
그리고 카트에 공급,
and supplies in the cart,
아무도 사람이 다쳐.
and nobody gets hurt.
우리는 당신이 우리의 공급을주는 경우에, 우리는 여기서 죽을거야.
If we give you our supplies,
we'll all die out here.
당신이하지 않으면, 당신은 바로 여기 죽을거야.
If you don't, you'll die right here.
그녀가 말한대로 수행합니다.
Do as she says.
지금!
Now!
- _ - _
- _
어떻게 당신의 믿음은, 장관을 들고있어?
How's your faith holding up, Chancellor?
닥쳐.
Shut up.
확고한.
Unwavering.
당신은이 작업을 수행 할 수 없습니다.
You don't want to do this.
산책 그만!
Stop walking!
우리 모두는 더 나은 삶을 찾고 여기 온
We all came out here
searching for a better life,
당신과 동일합니다.
same as you.
어쩌면 우리는 그것을 찾을 수 있습니다
Maybe we can find it
우리는 함께 일합니다.
if we work together.
감사합니다 ...
Thanks...
하지만.
But no.
_
이제, 멀리 카트에서 모두,
Now, everyone, back away from the cart
하고 무릎 꿇고.
and get on your knees.
지금!
Now!
그녀가 말하는 마십시오.
Do what she says.
당신, 너무.
You, too.
아, 깜짝 무엇. 당신은 다른 사람 같아.
Oh, what a surprise. You're
just like everyone else.
행운을 빌어 요.
Good luck, John.
말해봐. 당신은 무엇을 보는가?
Talk to me. What do you see?
당신의 눈을 닫습니다.
Close your eyes.
밑 구덩이를 상상해 보라.
Imagine a bottomless pit.
그냥 스틱.
Just stick with it.
단테의 좌표에 따르면,
According to Dante's coordinates,
당신은 거의 다 왔어.
you're almost there.
최종에 무슨 일 이죠?
What's happening on your end?
그들은 Tondc 대피 했습니까?
Did they evacuate Tondc?
아직 알고 있지만, 클라크의하지 마십시오.
Don't know yet, but it's Clarke.
그녀는 그것을 끝낼 수 있습니다.
She'll get it done.
그냥 그 배출구를 통해 엉덩이를 쥐에 집중
Just concentrate on squeezing
your ass through that vent
당신의 여동생에 대한 걱정 중지합니다.
and stop worrying about your sister.
옥타 비아 Tondc에서의?
Octavia's in Tondc?
그녀는 거기에?
She's there?
레이븐.
Raven.
그녀는거야 괜찮을거야.
She's gonna be ok.
클라크는 여기서졌습니다.
Clarke fired out of here.
그녀는거야 시간에 목적지에 도착.
She's gonna get there on time.
어떻게 나 한테이를 지킬 수있다?
How could you keep this from me?
클라크는 당신을 보호하기 위해 노력했다.
Clarke was trying to protect you.
들어 봐. 당신은 여전히?? 할 일이있다.
Listen. You still have a job to do.
난 당신이 옥타 비아 걱정 알고
I know you're worried about Octavia,
하지만 당신은 집중해야합니다.
but you have to focus.
그냥이 작업을 수행하자.
Let's just get this done.
회의에있을 경우,
Should be at the meeting,
당신과 함께 나무를보고하지.
not watching the trees with you.
조용한. 거기에 사람이있다.
Quiet. There's someone out there.
이 하나의 광산, 하늘 소녀.
This one's mine, Sky girl.
Atohl?
링컨?
Lincoln?
당신은 뭐하는거야?
What are you doing?
그를 멀리에서 얻을.
Get away from him.
- GAH! - 나는 그에게서 도망했다!
- Gah!
- I said get away from him!
당신은 이해하지 않습니다.
You don't understand.
나는 그것을 싸울 수 없습니다.
I can't fight it.
그렇습니다, 당신은 할 수있다. 우리는 할 수 있습니다.
Yes, you can. We can.
나는 당신의 형제를 배신.
I betrayed your brother.
그는 나 때문에 산에서 죄수입니다.
He's a prisoner in the
mountain because of me.
링컨, 난 당신 둘 사이에 무슨 일이 있었는지 모른다
Lincoln, I don't know what
happened between you two,
하지만 벨라미는, 그가 괜찮했다.
but Bellamy made it, he's fine.
우리는 우리 내부에 사람이있어.
We've got our inside man.
지금은 당신이 나와 함께해야합니다.
Now I need you to come with me.
아악!
Unh!
_
땅볼은 포기하지 않습니다.
Grounders don't give up.
우리는 싸울.
We fight.
어느 쪽이든 당신은 일어나서 우리는이 싸움,
Either you get up and we fight this,
또는 당신은 멀리 크롤링하고 겁쟁이처럼 혼자 죽는다.
or you crawl away and
die alone like a coward.
그것은 당신의 선택입니다.
It's your choice.
존.
John.
어서. 우리는 가야 해.
Come on. We got to go.
가. 그는이야. 그것은 시간이다.
There. He's up. It's about time.
조용한, 카스피.
Quiet, Caspian.
너 괜찮아?
You all right?
그가 아니라면, 우리는 여기에 그를 떠난다.
If he's not, we're leaving him here.
난 괜찮아.
I'm ok.
그것은 집에 갈 시간이다.
It's time to go home.
그리고 그것은 정확히 어디입니까?
And where exactly is that?
선생님, 난 당신이 더 나은 곳으로 우리를 데려 위해 노력하고 알고
Sir, I know you're trying
to take us to a better place,
하지만 주위를 둘러 봐.
but look around.
우리는 우리가 더 물가있어, 어떤 음식가있어
We've got no food, we've got no water,
더 생각하는 방법을 찾을 수 없습니다.
and no idea how to find it.
때문에 북쪽.
Due north.
그녀는 정북 말했다.
She said due north.
북쪽으로 인해, 존 무엇입니까?
What is due north, John?
그녀는 빛의 도시에 대해 얘기했다.
She was talking about the City of Light.
그녀는 그런 말을 했습니까?
Did she say that?
하지 마십시오.
No.
그녀는 얼마나 멀리 북쪽으로 인해 말을 했습니까?
Did she say how far due north?
아니 그녀는하지 않았다, 그러나 그녀는 우리를 거기에 전송되지 않을 것이다
No. She didn't, but she
wouldn't be sending us there
우리는 그것을 만들 수없는 경우.
if we couldn't make it.
그게 누군 데? 거짓말 쟁이와 도둑
Who's that? The liar and the thief
누가 우리를 강탈하고 기절?
who robbed us and knocked you out?
선생님, 정말 당신이 고려되지 않습니다 바랍니다.
Sir, I really hope you
are not considering this.
존, 우리는 아무 무기도없고 식량이 없습니다.
John, we have no weapons and no rations.
우리가 북쪽으로 이동하고 잘못이 있다면,
If we go north and you're wrong,
그 다음 우리 모두는 죽을 것이다.
then all of us will die.
지금 여기서 돌아 가면, 우리는 살고있다.
If we turn back now, we live.
그게 다야?
So that's it?
우리는 돌아올 수없는 지점에 도달했습니다?
We've reached the point of no return?
당신은 그냥 포기하고 싶지?
You just want to give up?
나는 그런 말을하지 않았다.
I didn't say that.
당신도 말하지 않았다.
You didn't not say it either.
즉 북극성이다.
That is the North Star.
먼저 가세요.
After you.
나머지는 스스로 결정해야합니다,
The rest of you need to
decide for yourselves,
하지만 어느 쪽이든, 우리는 당신을 위해 다시 오죠
but either way, we'll come back for you
우리는 그것을 발견 할 때.
when we find it.
선생님, 이건 실수입니다.
Sir, this is a mistake.
당신은 그것을 찾을거야, 당신은 성공하지 못할 거예요.
You're not gonna find it,
you're not gonna make it.
저는 믿습니다 ...
I believe...
이것은 그들이, 존 믿음을 가지고 부르는 것이다.
this is what they call having faith, John.
믿음?
Faith?
아니. 그냥 할 수있는 더 나은 아무것도있다.
Nah. Just got nothing better to do.
친구는 정식 코드, 선생님이 필요합니다.
Pal needs your auth code, sir.
확인을 클릭합니다. 동작합니다.
Ok. Activated.
그녀는 라이브입니다.
She's live.
휘트먼, 당신은 위치에있다? 이상.
Whitman, are you in position? Over.
차별 철폐, 선생님.
Affirmative, sir.
목표를 생성하는 것은 지금 조정합니다. 이상.
Generating target coordinates now. Over.
클라크, 우리는 계속 이동해야합니다.
Clarke, we have to keep moving.
우리는 충분히 멀리 아니에요.
We're not far enough away.
마지막으로 그들은 미사일을 사용
The last time they used a missile,
제가 태어나 기 전에이었다.
it was before I was born.
전설에 따르면, 그것은 숲에 구멍을 왼쪽
According to legend, it
left a hole in the woods
당신은에서 볼 수 없었다.
you could not see across.
이제 가자.
Now let's go.
우리가 그들을 그리워 한 경우?
What if we made them miss?
당신은 듣고 아닙니다.
You're not listening.
그런 무기로, 당신은 놓칠 수 없다.
With a weapon like that, you can't miss.
그렇습니다, 당신은 할 수있다. 나는 그들을 감시인에 대해 얘기 들어
Yes, you can. I heard them
talking about a spotter,
현장에서 누군가가 미사일을 목표로합니다.
someone in the field to aim the missile.
우리는 그를 찾을 수 있다면.
If we could just find him.
아니 무엇 그녀는 여기서 뭐하는거야?
No. What's she doing here?
클라크는, 요, 다시 갈 수 없습니다.
Clarke, yo, can't go back.
클라크!
Clarke!
북한이 38도 54 분, 0.25 초.
North 38 degrees, 54 minutes, .25 seconds.
복사.
Copy.
서쪽으로 77도에 의해,
By west 77 degrees,
이분, 0.12 초.
2 minutes, .12 seconds.
이상.
Over.
우리는 혔어.
We're locked in.
확인을 위해 대기.
Standing by for confirmation.
엄마, 여기서 뭐하는거야?
Mom, what are you doing here?
난 다시 캠프에 머물 당신을 말했다.
I told you to stay back at camp.
충분히, 클라크. 나는 장관 해요.
Enough, Clarke. I'm the chancellor.
나는 이동하려면 사용 권한이 필요하지 않습니다 ...
I don't need your permission to go...
아니 우리는 지금 떠나야합니다.
No. We have to leave now.
무슨 일이야?
What is going on?
우리는 여기에있을 수 없습니다.
We can't be here.
엄마, 난 당신을 구걸하고있다. 하십시오.
Mom, I am begging you. Please.
어서.
Come on.
사령관은 어디? 클라크 어디있어?
Where's the commander? Where's Clarke?
모르겠어요.
I don't know.
나는 그들을보고 마지막으로, 그들은 아래층으로 향하고 있었다.
Last time I saw them, they
were heading downstairs.
그들은 지금이 아니에요.
They're not there now.
우리는 숲을 검색해야합니다.
We should search the woods.
나는 동의합니다.
I agree.
나는 다른 사람을 말할 것이다.
I'll tell the others.
최종 목표는 확인했다.
Final targets confirmed.
우리는 시작에 갈 수 있습니다.
We are go for launch.
당신의 명령에, 선생님.
On your command, sir.
화재.
Fire.
조류는 공기이다.
Bird is in the air.
(10)에 미치는 영향, 9 ...
Impact in 10, 9...
잠깐!
Wait!
아니, 지금 중지 할 수 없습니다. 시간이 없어.
No. We can't stop. There's no time.
내가 한 단계 더 복용하고 있지 않다
I am not taking a step further
당신이 때까지 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 말해.
until you tell me what is happening.
5, 4, 3,
2,1.
2, 1.
엄마.
Mom.
엄마, 괜찮아요?
Mom, are you ok?
오, 맙소사.
Oh, my God.
어서. 우리는 여기에있을 수 없습니다.
Come on. We can't be here.
우리는 ... 우리는 가야한다.
We... we have to go.
당신은 알고 있었다.
You knew.
당신은 알고, 당신은이 일이 일어 나도록?
You knew, and you let this happen?
우리는 선택의 여지가 없었다.
We had no choice.
그래서 많은 사람들.
So many people.
우리 사람들.
Our people.
아니 우리는 벨라미를 보호했다.
No. We had to protect Bellamy.
그없이 ...
Without him...
아, 그만!
Oh, stop it!
나는 그것을 듣고 싶지 않아.
I don't want to hear it.
엄마 ...
Mom...
말해이 LEXA이었다.
Tell me this was Lexa.
제발, 클라크.
Please, Clarke.
이것은 당신이 아니었다 알려주세요.
Please tell me this wasn't you.
나는 내가 할 수있는 바랍니다.
I wish I could.
당신이 누구에게도 말할 수 없습니다.
You can't tell anyone about this.
누군가는 우리가 알고 있다는 것을 발견하면,
If anyone finds out that we knew,
12 가문의 동맹이 끊어집니다.
the alliance of the 12 clans will break.
우리는 전쟁을 잃게됩니다.
We'll lose the war.
당신은 선을 넘어.
You crossed the line.
엄마.
Mom.
그들의 피가 손에
Their blood is on your hands,
그리고 우리가 이길 경우에도,
and even if we win,
난 당신이 시간을 씻어 수 없습니다 두려워.
I'm afraid you won't be able
to wash it off this time.
걱정하지 마십시오.
Don't worry.
당신의 비밀은 나와 함께 안전합니다.
Your secret is safe with me.
엄마는 ... 기다립니다.
Mom... Wait.
엄마!
Mom!
무슨 일이 너무 오래 벨라미를 복용?
What's taking Bellamy so long?
모르겠어요.
I don't know.
어쩌면 그들은 그를 붙 잡았다.
Maybe they caught him.
아뇨,이 방법을 알아낼 것이다, 알아요.
No. He'll figure a way out, I know he will.
재스퍼, 이미 4시간되었습니다.
Jasper, it's already been 4 hours.
경비원은 다시 어떤 초있을 것입니다.
The guards will be back any second.
여자들은 다른 사람을하고 있습니다.
They're gonna take someone else.
제 말을 들어.
No. Listen to me.
여러분, 우리는 계획대로.
Everyone, we stick to the plan.
그들은 다른 사람을 복용하지 않을
They're not taking anyone else
싸움없이이 방 밖으로!
out of this room without a fight!
준비.
Get ready.
분산.
Disperse.
이거요.
This one.
네, 부인.
Yes, ma'am.
하지 마십시오! 하지 마십시오! 하지 마십시오!
No! No! No!
이봐! 그 손 치워!
Hey! Get your hands off him!
- 그만! - 움직이지 마!
- Enough!
- Don't move!
대신 데려가.
Take him instead.
아니, 당신은 할 수 없습니다!
No, you can't!
일어나.
Get up.
하지 마십시오!
No!
재스퍼! 재스퍼하지!
Jasper! Not Jasper!
나머지를 검색합니다.
Search the rest.
다른 무기가 없는지 확인합니다.
Make sure there are no other weapons.
네, 부인. 당신은 그녀를 들었다. 가자!
Yes, ma'am. You heard her. Let's go!
즉시 우리가 실험실에서있는 한,
As soon as we're in the lab,
나는 그가 수험 공부를 할 수 있습니다.
I want him prepped.
우리는 즉시 시작합니다.
We start immediately.
알았다. 자산 운반, 엘리베이터 "C."
Copy that. Transporting
asset, elevator "C."
윽. 뭔가 잘못입니다.
Ugh. Something's wrong.
아악! 방사선.
Unh! Radiation.
우리는 여기서 나가야 할 필요가있다.
We need to get out of here.
내 피부!
My skin!
봉쇄 위반 레벨 5.
Containment breach level 5.
전체 바닥을 밀봉.
Seal the whole floor.
벨라미.
Bellamy.
당신은에 외부 공기를 끌어있어
You got to pull the outside air in
공기 여과 시스템을 반전시키기.
to reverse the air filtration system.
심지어 일하고 경우 그냥 우리가 알고있는 방법을 말해.
Just tell me how we know
if it's even working.
봉쇄 위반.
Containment breach.
나는 일하고 말할 것입니다.
I'd say it's working.
, 대통령 님 감사합니다.
Thank you, Mr. President.
가자! 이것은 우리의 기회입니다!
Let's go! This is our chance!
모두 이동!
Everybody move!
레벨을 가지고!
Take the level!
몬티, 카메라를 얻을.
Monty, get the cameras.
밀러는 자신의 총을 얻을.
Miller, get their guns.
이동!
Go!
아니 당신은 할 수 없습니다.
No. You can't.
난 당신이 우리에게 매우 특별한 거 알아 바랍니다.
I hope you know that you're
incredibly special to us.
누가 그들에게 도움이?
Who helped them?
나는 당신이 무슨 말을하는지 모르겠어요.
I don't know what you're talking about.
당신은 여전히?? 영향을,
You still have influence,
당신을 믿는 사람들,
people who believe in you,
그 중 하나는 레벨 5 오늘 조사.
and one of them irradiated level 5 today.
내가 누구인지 알고 싶어요.
I want to know who it is.
그것은 날이었다.
It was me.
음, 누구든지 당신을 도움
Well, you and whoever helped you
오늘 우리의 사람들 (11) 사망,
killed 11 of our people today,
무엇을 위해서?
and for what?
우리는 곧 자신의 수준을 탈환 낼거야.
We're gonna retake their level soon enough.
내 시야, 케이지의 나가.
Get out of my sight, Cage.
나는 우리가 동의하지 알고 ...
I know we disagree...
하지만이 모든 곧 끝날 것입니다.
but this will all be over soon.
오늘 Tondc을 폭격.
I bombed Tondc today.
아버지는, 케이지 우리를 보호하기 위해 그 사일로를 설치했습니다.
My father installed that
silo to protect us, Cage.
왜 내가 할 노력하고있어 정확히 어떤 것을 볼 수없는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Why can't you see that that is
exactly what I'm trying to do?
클라크 사령관의 죽음과 함께,
With Clarke and the commander dead,
야만인은 서로를 죽이는에 돌아갈 수
the savages can go back
to killing each other,
그리고, 우리는 지상 치를 수 있습니다.
and then we can retake the ground.
그리고 그것은 단지 당신에게 당신의 영혼을 비용!
And it only cost you your souls!
그는 준비.
He's ready.
당신은 뭐하는거야?
What are you doing?
당신을 자유롭게.
Freeing you.
그를 제지합니다.
Restrain him.
진정해. 그를 다치게하지 마십시오.
Easy, easy. Do not hurt him.
골수는 48 시간에서 차기.
The marrow kicks in in 48 hours.
당신은 언젠가 나 한테 감사합니다.
You'll thank me someday.
- 동기화 및 chamallow에 의해 수정 - - www.addic7ed.com -
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -